<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yunxiao Cai</title>
    <link>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yunxiao Cai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clone</title>
      <link>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/clone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/clone/</guid>
      <description>Clone is a 2D platformer made in Unity. - I developed weapon system and UI for this game. - Team: Yunxiao Cai (Gameplay, UI) Christian Boyd (Gameplay, Enemy AI, Player Movement) Dong Wang (Gameplay, Enemy AI) Liam Scott (Level Design) Tanner McDougal (2D Art)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FightBackSlime!</title>
      <link>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/slime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/slime/</guid>
      <description>FightBackSlime! is a 2D casual game developed in Unity. - One day I knocked my roommate(Jinrui)&amp;rsquo;s door and asked him: &amp;ldquo;Do you have any interesting small casual game idea?&amp;rdquo; He smiled and answered me: &amp;ldquo;Sure, let&amp;rsquo;s start from this one.&amp;rdquo;   - Team: Yunxiao Cai(Gameplay, UI Programming, Enemy AI, Animation State Machine) Jinrui Hu(2D Art, Game Design)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fighters</title>
      <link>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/fighters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/fighters/</guid>
      <description>Fighters is a 2D dual player fighting game made in Pygame. - I developed damage calculation logic and characters movement for this game.   - Team: Yunxiao Cai (Gameplay, Damage Calculation Logic, Characters Movement) Cameron Kern (Gameplay, Characters Movement) Sean Grillone (2D Art)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lontarot</title>
      <link>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/lontarot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/lontarot/</guid>
      <description>Lontarot is a 2.5D platformer made in Unity. I did visual effect, inventory system, UI programming and story writing for this game. - A particle effect created by me for an ability of the main character. - The menu directly inherit from my MenuLayer script. Link to my MenuLayer Code Sample https://github.com/Lutetium0/LontarotUICodeSample/blob/master/MenuLayer.cs - The inventory inherit from my VerticalScrollMenuLayer script.  Link to my VerticalScrollMenuLayer Script Code Sample https://github.com/Lutetium0/LontarotUICodeSample/blob/master/VerticalScrollMenuLayer.cs - The inventory menu is changing its display when players click confirm button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MultiUserSpreadsheet</title>
      <link>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/multiuserspreadsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/multiuserspreadsheet/</guid>
      <description>MultiUserSpreadsheet is a project developed in Windows Forms(Client) and Linux(Server) which allows multiple users to connect to the same spreadsheet and edit cells in spreadsheet simultaneously. - A screenshot of the client developed by me in Windows Forms.  Link to my code sample for this client https://github.com/Lutetium0/MultiUserSpreadsheetClientSample/blob/master/Form1.cs - Team: Yunxiao Cai(Client, Network) Dong Wang(Server, Network) Rong Xiao(Server, Network)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pill</title>
      <link>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/thepill/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lutetium0.github.io/Portfolio/blogs/thepill/</guid>
      <description>The Pill is an 3D animation made in Unreal Engine 4. - I developed the lighting effect from 2:53 to 3:06 with Unreal Blueprint. I also made the animation sequence from 3:07 to 3:21.  A screenshot of my blueprint for that light effect. - Team: Yunxiao Cai (Lighting, Material, Animation) Bryce Woodell (Cinematography, Editing) Jess Ulloa (Cinematography, Sound, Music, Environment) Austin Gibbons (Animation, Cinematography, Editing) Butros Ajami (Environment, Editing, Story elements) Isaac Smith (Cinematography, Editing, Texturing, Animation) Dassan Verstrepen (Cinematography, Editing) Scott Foden (Editing, Cinematography, Animation) Wess Lancaster (Music, Animation, Produce) Jack McCarthy</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>